

I'm a result oriented frontend developer with experience in creating Landing Pages and SPA, using React(JS/TS), Redux, HTML & CSS. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies.

My free time is dedicated to improve my programming skills and boosting my English. I would like to find a full-time job in a creative company with up-to-date task and collaborative team!

### Contact



@leonid\_kr



+375 (25) 751-95-35



xx13.02@gmail.com



Belarus, Minsk

## Skills

- REACT/REDUX
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- HTML5/CSS3
- AXIOS/REST API
- Unit tests/StoryBook
- GIT

### Languages

- English Pre-Intermediate (in progress)
- Russian
- Polish (B1)

# **LEONID KRUCHENOK**

FRONT-END DEVELOPER







**PORTFOLIO** 

# **Work Experience**

#### **PART-TIME EMPLOYMENT**

Front-end developer | Sep. 2021 - present

Took part in creating learning app, developed login page, modal windows, tests, menu. Use next deleloper technologies: React/Redux / ReduxThunk/RestApi/Axios/ReduxForm/Fo rmik /MaterialUI/SCSS, etc. Use TypeScript for best control of the code in work.

#### **INDIVIDUAL ENTREPRENEUR**

Create targeted advertising on Instagram & Facebook | 2018 - Sep. 2021

- Communication with customers
- Create ads in social networks
- Development of promotion strategies

# **Education History**

#### **IT-INCUBATOR**

Front-end developer | React & Redux

- 2021
- React, Redux, Typescript, REST, Git, Team development ...

#### **HTML ACADEMY, 2020**

 JavaScript for begginers, HTML and CSS for begginers

#### **IPK RIPO COLLEGE**

Industrial and civil construction

• 2014- 2018 | Builder Technician